http://www.d3o.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
www.d3o.com uses cookies to enhance your experience. Find out more about cookies.
> Privacy Policy
At D3O we are committed to ensuring and protecting your privacy at any time you are on our website or communicating electronically with our personnel.
Our Privacy Policy is contained below and provides a detailed explanation as to how we may use the personal information you give us, or any we collect through legal means.
Updates of our Privacy Policy are completed frequently, thus you should peruse this Policy habitually.
1. INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM YOU:
Data is collected and processed when you use the D3O website. The following are approved methods of collection:
1.1 If you register for information by filling out our Contact Us form we can collect the information provided and hold for a minimum of seven (7) years.1.2 Traffic data, weblogs, location data, and any other communication can be collected. These details come from your visit to our site and any resource tools you use while on the site.1.3 Any communication on our website or to personnel allows us to collect information.1.4 All information or data provided are the exclusive property of D3O save any clause in this policy that renders redundant that right.
2. USE OF COOKIES:
2.1 Circumstances may arise when we may need to gather information about your computer to help provide appropriate services or products to you. The data gathered from this process is solely statistical data, which may be shared with third-party advertisers.2.2 The facts D3O collects about you through cookies are statistical only. No identifying information will be shared about our visitors and how they made use of our site.2.3 Cookies are used to collect general online usage by using a cookie file, which is stored on your browser. For more information about how we use cookies, please refer to our Cookie Policy.2.4 Any computer has the option to decline cookies. Your web browser options include an “enable” button to decline cookies. It is imperative that you understand by declining cookies you may be limiting your access to sections of our website and its functionality.2.5 We do not have control over cookies used by third-party websites or advertisers, however there is information on how to turn them off in our Cookie Policy.
2.6. Google Analytics: Google Analytics is a web analytics service. Web analysis is the gathering, collection and analysis of data about the behaviour of visitors to websites.  A web analysis is mainly used to optimize a website and for the cost-benefit analysis of Internet advertising.2.6.1 Google Analytics Advertising Features integrated on our site: We have integrated the component Google Advertising and Analytics features on this website. These features allow:
Remarketing with Google Analytics;Google Display Network Impression Reporting;Integrated services that require Google Analytics to collect data for advertising purposes; including the collection of data via advertising cookies and identifiers.
The operator of the Google Advertising and Analytics component is Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Pkwy, Mountain View, CA 94043-1351, USA.2.6.2 How the Cookies are used: Google Analytics uses cookies. The information generated by the cookie about your use of this site is usually transmitted to a Google server in the USA and stored there. Google may transfer the personal information collected via this technical procedure to third parties.On our behalf, Google will use this information to evaluate your use of this site, compile reports on this site activity and to provide further services related to this site and internet use to us.2.6.3 How to opt-out: You can prevent the storage of cookies by a corresponding setting of your browser software; however, please note that if you do this, you may not be able to use all the features of this site to the fullest extent possible.In addition, you may prevent the collection of the data generated by the cookie and related to your use of the website (including your IP address) by Google as well as the processing of this data by Google by downloading and installing the browser plug-in available under the following link: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=enThis browser add-on informs Google Analytics via JavaScript that no data and information about website visits may be transmitted to Google Analytics.In addition, a cookie already set by Google Analytics can be deleted at any time via the Internet browser or other software programs.Our site uses Google Analytics performance reports relating to demographics and interests and reports on Google Display Network impressions. You can disable Google Analytics for display advertising and customize the ads on the Google Display Network by visiting the ad settings at this link: https://adssettings.google.com.2.7. Facebook Pixel Cookies and LinkedIn Insight Tag Cookies: We have also integrated Facebook Pixel Cookies and LinkedIn Insight Tag Cookies on this website. More information on these Cookies can be found at:Facebook Pixel Cookies: https://www.facebook.com/business/help/471978536642445?id=1205376682832142LinkedIn Insight Tag Cookies: https://www.linkedin.com/help/linkedin/answer/65521?query=Insight%20tag%20&hcppcid=search
3. USE OF YOUR INFORMATION:
Information stored and collected about you allows us to improve our services or products for you. Added to this parameter, we may use your information for the following purposes:
3.1 Any commitment we make on a contracted basis.3.2 If information is requested from our website concerning services or products offered, we may use your data. Products or services which may be of interest to you can also deem a communication from us, if permission has been granted.3.3 Notification re-changes or improvements may be sent to you in regards to product or service changes that could affect our service to you.3.4 Added use of your data may include permission for third parties to use your data. This permission would be granted by you in regards to unrelated products or services that may be in your interests. We or third parties can only contact you in regards to this information if consent has been provided for information collection.3.6 Third party contact or communications from our website, as a new customer, is only made if you have granted us permission. These communications are only offered for information you consented to and no other unrelated information.3.7 Data that you do not want us to use or third parties to use can be withheld, once consent has been given regarding our collection of your data. We will always provide you with an opportunity to decline communications and our or third party data usage.
4. STORING YOUR PERSONAL DATA:
4.1 Outside of the European Economic Area are places for storing and processing data we collect from you. We may take advantage of these outside areas, allowing a staff to process data collected from you. These processors may work for our suppliers. The transfer of this data may include processing and completing your order on our site, such as utilising your payment information or offering support services. We take all reasonable processes to ensure your data is secure and in agreement with our Privacy Policy as outlined here.4.2 D3O will always use secure servers to ensure proper data storage. Information on transactions is kept encrypted for safety measures.4.3 Transmission of data on the internet can never be ultimately secure. We do not and cannot guarantee security of information collected electronically or transmitted; however, we take all reasonable endeavours to provide the best security available. As a result of our inability to guarantee safety, you are submitting information to us at your own risk.
5. DISCLOSING YOUR INFORMATION:
5.1 Personal information to third parties may be disclosed:5.2 This disclosure occurs when we sell all or a section of our business or assets to a third party.5.2.1 Personal information can be offered to any member of our company, such as subsidiaries, holding companies and their subsidiaries only if deemed appropriate.5.2.2 Legal or statutory requirements may mean a sharing of your information.5.2.3 Lowering credit risk and fraud protection may result in information disclosure.
6. THIRD PARTY LINKS:
Links might be discovered on our site that belongs to third parties. Any third-party website on our site has a privacy policy. You should check their terms. We do not accept liability or responsibility for their privacy policies, based on our lack of control over these third party links.
7. ACCESS TO INFORMATION:
The Data Protection Act 1998 was established to govern online electronic communications. The act gives you access to any data we have about you. Contact information is given below, which should be used to gain details about information we hold on you.
8. CONTACTING US:
Please do not hesitate to make any queries, comments or requests you may have regarding this Privacy Policy. You can contact us at info@d3o.com.
